陆成宇结婚这么多年
你从来没有正眼看过
就算你知道当年
那个陪在你身边的女人是我
应该也只会觉得恶心吧
我从来没有这么想过
他是这么跟你说的是
石桥迈亲口告诉我
你骂他像头猪一样
他果然是为了那句话在发脾气
我当时确实生气
口不择言
但我没有想侮辱他呀
成语你别跟他解释那么多了
他就是荞麦派来报复我们的
荞麦现在人在哪
你联系得到他吗
为什么我一直找他他都不出现
甚至我去给他送离婚协议书
他都不出现
因为那个时候的我
还九死一生的躺在病床上
只想减掉那身被你们嘲笑的肥肉啊
郭成宇我今天过来呢
肩膀
没有见到荞麦我是不会牵的
Lu Chengyu has been married for so many years
You've never looked at it.
Even if you knew that year
The woman who is by your side is me
It should only feel disgusting
I never thought of it that way.
Is that what he told you?
Mai Ishiqiao told me himself
You scold him like a pig
He was really angry about that sentence
I was angry.
unspoken
But I didn't mean to insult him.
Idiom, don't explain so much to him
He was sent by Buckwheat to take revenge on us.
Where is Buckwheat now?
Can you contact him?
Why did I keep looking for him and he never showed up?
I even sent him the divorce papers
He doesn't show up
Because of me at that time
Still lying in the hospital bed
I just want to lose the fat that you laugh at
Guo Chengyu, I'm here today
The shoulder.
I won't pull it without seeing buckwheat